<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DoNotLate</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--로그인 페이지-->
    <string name="login_top_title1">Welcome</string>
    <string name="login_top_title2"></string>
    <string name="login_top_title3">Please proceed to log in.</string>
    <string name="login_edit_text1">Please enter your e-mail.</string>
    <string name="login_edit_text2">Please enter your password.</string>
    <string name="login_text1">Please check your email.</string>
    <string name="login_text2">Passwords do not match.</string>
    <string name="login_text3">Don\&apos;t have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_text4">Or sign up with</string>
    <string name="login_sign_up_line"><u>Sign Up</u></string>

    <!--회원가입 페이지-->
    <string name="sign_up_top_title1">Or sign up with</string>
    <string name="sign_up_top_title2"></string>
    <string name="sign_up_top_title3">Shall we go make an appointment now?</string>
    <string name="sign_up_edit_text1">Please enter your nickname.</string>
    <string name="sign_up_edit_text2">Please re-enter your password.</string>
    <string name="sign_up_text1">Nickname contains special characters.</string>
    <string name="sign_up_text2">Please make your password a combination of 8 to 20 letters and numbers.</string>
    <string name="sign_up_text3">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up_login_line"><u>Login</u></string>

    <!--정산하기 첫 페이지-->
    <string name="cal_top_title1"></string>
    <string name="cal_text1">Consumption analysis</string>
    <string name="cal_text2">Total expenditure\n\n</string>
    <string name="cal_text3">Promise of progress\n\n</string>
    <string name="cal_text4">Settlement in progress</string>
    <string name="cal_text5">There is a record of the payment not being completed.</string>
    <string name="cal_text6">Settlement details</string>
    <string name="cal_text7">Settlement has been completed.</string>
    <string name="cal_btn_text">Calculate</string>

    <!--정산하기 첫 페이지(Activity)-->
    <string name="cal_activity_text1"><![CDATA["￦"]]></string>
    <string name="cal_activity_text2">EA</string>
    <string name="cal_activity_text3">Want to change your settlement status?</string>
    <string name="cal_activity_text4">Yes</string>
    <string name="cal_activity_text5">No</string>

    <!--정산하기 두번째 페이지-->
    <string name="cal2_top_title1">Shall we start the settlement?</string>
    <string name="cal2_top_title2"></string>
    <string name="cal2_top_title3">Please enter settlement history.</string>
    <string name="cal2_text1">Expenditure title</string>
    <string name="cal2_text2">Expenditure date</string>
    <string name="cal2_text3">Expenditure category</string>
    <string name="cal2_edit_text1">Please enter a description of your expenses.</string>
    <string name="cal2_edit_text2">Please select the date by clicking\nthe icon.</string>
    <string name="cal2_btn_text">Next</string>

    <!--정산하기 두번째 페이지(Fragment)-->
    <string name="cal_frgment_text1">Please fill out all fields.</string>

    <!--정산하기 세번째 페이지-->
    <string name="cal3_top_title1">It\&apos;s coming to an end</string>
    <string name="cal3_top_title2"></string>
    <string name="cal3_top_title3">Please enter the settlement amount.</string>
    <string name="cal3_text1">Total settlement amount</string>
    <string name="cal3_text2">Penalty amount</string>
    <string name="cal3_text3">Number of people to divide the amount with</string>
    <string name="cal3_text4">people</string>
    <string name="cal3_edit_text1">Please enter the total amount\n to be settled.</string>
    <string name="cal3_edit_text2">Please enter the Penalty amount.</string>
    <string name="cal3_edit_text3">Please enter the Number of people\n to divide the amount with.</string>

    <!--정산하기 세번째 페이지(Fragment)-->
    <string name="cal1_frgment_text1">Add my fine</string>
    <string name="cal1_frgment_text2">Addition of fines to colleagues</string>

    <!--정산하기 세번째 페이지-->
    <string name="cal4_top_title1"></string>
    <string name="cal4_top_title2">This is the settlement result.</string>
    <string name="cal4_top_title3">Please check.</string>
    <string name="cal4_btn_text1">Settlement complete</string>
    <string name="cal4_btn_text2">Exit</string>

    <!--미니게임 페이지-->
    <string name="game_top_title1">Who is today’s winner?</string>
    <string name="game_top_title2">Mini game</string>
    <string name="game_text1">Roulette</string>
    <string name="game_text2">Ladder</string>

    <!--미니게임_룰렛 페이지-->
    <string name="game_roulette_text1">This is a game where prizes are selected \n from numbers 1 to 8 and won.</string>
    <string name="game_roulette_text2">Spin</string>

    <!--미니게임_룰렛 페이지-->
    <string name="roulette_text1">winning</string>
    <string name="roulette_text2">Spinning...?</string>

    <!--메인 페이지-->
    <string name="main_top_title1">You can become the promised king,</string>
    <string name="main_top_title2"></string>
    <string name="main_text1">Make\n an\n appointment</string>
    <string name="main_text2">My\n promise</string>
    <string name="main_text3">Place\n search</string>
    <string name="main_text4">Calculate</string>
    <string name="main_text5">Mini\n game</string>
    <string name="main_text6">Friend\n management</string>

    <!--친구 페이지-->
    <string name="friend_text1">My friends list</string>
    <string name="friend_btn_text">Requested friend list</string>

    <!--친구요청 페이지-->
    <string name="friend_request_top_title">Shall we find a new friend?</string>
    <string name="friend_request_edit_text">Please search for the friend you\nwould like to request.</string>
    <string name="friend_request_btn_text">Click</string>
    <string name="friend_request_text">Please select the friends\nyou would like to invite.</string>

    <!--놀거리 페이지-->
    <string name="time">No information</string>

    <!--설정 페이지-->
    <string name="preference_file_key" translatable="false">darkModeOff</string>

    <!--법령-->
    <string name="info">
    Don\&apos;t Be Late Company establishes and discloses the personal information processing
        policy as follows in order to protect the personal information of information subjects
        and handle related complaints quickly and smoothly in accordance with Article 30 of the
        Personal Information Protection Act.\n
        ○ This privacy policy is effective from January 1, 2023.\n\n

Article 1(The purposes for which personal information is processed)\n

① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company processes personal information for the following purposes.
Personal information being processed will not be used for purposes other than the following,
and if the purpose of use changes, necessary measures will be taken,
such as obtaining separate consent in accordance with Article 18 of the Personal Information Protection Act.\n

1. Homepage membership registration and management.\n
- Personal information is processed for the purpose of confirming membership
registration and providing various noticesand notifications.\n\n


Article 2(The period for processing and retaining personal information)\n

① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company processes and retains personal information within
the personal information retention and use period pursuant to the law or
within the personal information retention and use period agreed upon
when collecting personal information from the information subject.\n

② The processing and retention period for each personal information is as follows.\n
1. Website membership registration and management: Until withdrawal from the website.
However, in the case of the following reasons, until the end of the relevant reason.\n
1) If an investigation, investigation, etc.
is in progress for violation of relevant laws and regulations,
until the end of the investigation or investigation,\n\n


Article 3(Provision of personal information to a third party)\n
① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company provides personal information to third parties only in cases that fall under
Articles 17 and 18 of the Personal Information Protection Act, including the consent of the information subject
and special provisions of the law, and does not exceed the original scope without the prior consent
of the information subject. It will not be processed or provided to third parties.\n\n


Article 4(Outsourcing personal information processing (if applicable.))\n\n


Article 5(The rights and obligations of data subjects and legal representatives, and how to exercise such rights)\n
① The information subject may exercise his/her rights,
such as requesting viewing, correction, deletion, and suspension of processing of personal information,
at any time against Don\&apos;t Be Late Company.\n② The exercise of rights pursuant to Paragraph 1 may be made to
Don\&apos;t Be Late Company through writing, e-mail, facsimile (FAX), etc. in accordance with Article 41(1)
of the Enforcement Decree of the Personal Information Protection Act,
and Don\&apos;t Be Late Company will respond to this without delay. We will take action.\n
- [Enforcement Rule Annex No. 8] Request for personal information (viewing, correction/deletion, suspension of processing)\n
③ The exercise of rights under paragraph 1 may be done through an agent,
such as the information subject\&apos;s legal representative or a person authorized to do so.
In this case, you must submit a power of attorney in the format of Appendix 11 of the Enforcement Rules of
the Personal Information Protection Act.\n
- [Enforcement Rules Annex No. 11] Power of Attorney\n
④ Requests to view and suspend processing of personal information may limit the information
subject\&apos;s rights pursuant to Article 35, Paragraph 5 and Article 37, Paragraph 2 of the Personal Information Protection Act.\n
⑤ Requests for correction or deletion of personal information cannot be requested
if the personal information is specified as a collection target in other laws and regulations.\n
⑥ Don\&apos;t Be Late Company confirms whether the person making the request,
such as a request for viewing, a request for correction or deletion, or a request for suspension of processing,
is the person or a legitimate agent in accordance with the information subject\&apos;s rights.\n\n


Article 6(Personal information items processed)\n
① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company processes the following personal information items.\n
1. Personal information file name :  home page Profile\n
2. Personal information items : (Required items) ID, password, name(or nick-name), email\n
② The following personal information items may be automatically created and collected during the use of Internet services.\n
- IP address, cookie, MAC address, service use record, visit record, bad use record, etc.\n\n


Article 7 (Destruction of personal information)\n
① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company destroys personal information without delay when personal information becomes unnecessary,
such as when the personal information retention period has passed or the purpose of processing has been achieved.\n
② In cases where personal information must continue to be preserved pursuant to other laws
and regulations despite the expiration of the personal information retention period agreed upon
by the information subject or the purpose of processing has been achieved, the personal information
(or personal information file) shall be stored in a separate database (DB) Move it to
or store it in a different storage location to preserve it.\n
③ The procedures and methods for destroying personal information are as follows.\n
1. Destruction procedure\n
- Although it is late, the Company establishes a personal information destruction plan
and destroys personal information (or personal information files) that must be destroyed.\n
- Although it is late, the Company selects the personal information (or personal information file)
for which the reason for destruction occurred, Personal information (or personal information files)
will be destroyed with the approval of the personal information protection manager.\n
2. Method of destruction\n
- It\&apos;s Be Late Company destroys personal information recorded and stored
in electronic files so that the records cannot be reproduced, and if there is
personal information recorded or stored in paper documents, it is destroyed by shredding or incineration.\n\n


Article 8 (Measures to ensure the safety of personal information)\n
① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company is taking the following measures to ensure the safety of personal information.\n
1. Conduct regular self-audits\n
- To ensure the stability of personal information handling, we conduct self-audits on a regular basis (quarterly).\n\n


Article 9 (Matters regarding installation, operation and refusal of automatic personal information collection devices)\n
① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company does not use <![CDATA["cookies"]]> to store and frequently retrieve
the information subject\&apos;s usage information.\n\n


Article 10 (Personal Information Protection Manager)\n
① Don\&apos;t Be Late Company is responsible for the overall management of personal information processing,
and has designated a personal information protection manager as follows to handle complaints and provide relief
for damage from information subjects related to personal information processing.\n
 - Personal information protection officer\n
Department: Don\&apos;t Be Late Company\n
name : KIM JAE HYUN, LIM CHAE MYUNG, JANG GYU SIK, CHOI JI WON, PARK HYE LAN\n
rank : Leader, deputy leader, team member, team member, team member\n
contact : onecoin789@gmail.com, limchaem0318@gmail.com, jgs288@gmail.com, sp202401jw@gmail.com, tnfl2644@gmail.com\n\n


Article 11 (Request to view personal information)\n
① The information subject may request to view personal information pursuant to Article 35
of the Personal Information Protection Act to the department below.
Don\&apos;t Be Late Companywill endeavor to promptly process the information subject\&apos;s request to view personal information.\n
② Information subjects can inquire about all personal information protection-related inquiries,
complaint handling, damage relief, etc. to the personal information protection manager and responsible department.
Don\&apos;t Be Late Company will respond and process inquiries from information subjects without delay.\n
- Personal information access request reception and processing department\n
(Same as personal information protection manager)\n\n


Article 12 (Methods for relief from rights infringement)\n
① In order to receive relief from personal information infringement,
the information subject may apply for dispute resolution or consultation
to the Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee,
the Korea Internet, Security Agency\&apos;s Personal Information Infringement Reporting Center, etc.
In addition, for reporting and consultation regarding other personal information infringements,
please contact the organizations below.\n\n
1. Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee : 1833-6972 (www.kopico.go.kr)\n
2. Personal Information Infringement Reporting Center : 118 (privacy.kisa.or.kr)\n
3. Supreme Prosecutors\&apos; Office : 1301 (www.spo.go.kr)\n
4. National Police Agency : 182 (ecrm.cyber.go.kr)\n\n


Article 13 (Changes to personal information processing policy)\n
① This personal information processing policy is effective from August 22, 2022.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="personal">
Consent on collection and use of personal information\n\n

Don\&apos;t Be Late Company is doing its best to protect workers\&apos; personal information
by complying with the personal information protection regulations of related laws such as
the Personal Information Protection Act. Based on Article 17 of the Personal Information Protection Act,
the company wishes to obtain consent to collect, use, and store the user\&apos;s personal information
to the extent absolutely necessary and provide it to a third party.\n

 1. Purpose of collecting personal information\n
- Providing app features to users and third parties\n
 2. Collection items\n
- Personal information items : (Required items) ID, password, name(or nick-name), email\n
 3. Personal information retention and use period\n
- During the subscription period from the date of submission\n
 4. Refusal of consent to collection and use of personal information\n
- You can refuse the collection and use of personal information.
However, if you do not agree to the collection and use of personal information,
there may be restrictions on the use of the app.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="location">
Location-based service terms and conditions\n\n

Article 1 (Purpose)\n
The purpose of this agreement is to stipulate the rights, obligations and responsibilities,
and other necessary matters between Don\&apos;t Be Late company Corporation
(hereinafter referred to as the Company) and the subject of personal location information
in terms of the location-based services provided by the Company.\n\n


Article 2 (Working Rules Other Than the Terms of Use)\n
Matters not specified herein shall comply with the Act on the Protection and Use of Location Information,
Personal Information Protection Act, Act on Promotion of Information and Communications Network Utilization
and Information Protection, Framework Act on Telecommunications, Telecommunications Business Act
and other relevant regulations, terms of use and privacy policy of the Company,
and other guidelines as set forth by the Company.\n\n


Article 3 (Service contents and fees)\n
① Appointment making service: Provides a function that displays arrival time and distance
to the destination based on the current location through a chat room.\n
1. Appointment making service: Provides a function that displays the arrival time
and distance to the destination based on the current location through a chat room.\n
2. Search result and content using location information: where there is a request for information search,
or where the location information of the subject of personal location information or mobile device is provided,
such location information is used to provide search result, result of nearby location search (popular restaurants,
nearby businesses, means of transportation, etc.), and translation result\n
3. Provision of convenience services such as directions: optimal routes including traffic information,
directions, etc. are offered on a map, and locating nearby facilities, news and weather information,
emergency rescue service, automatic address completion and other convenience services shall be provided.\n
② Location-based services under paragraph (1) shall be offered free of charge.\n\n


Article 4 (Rights Held by Subjects of Personal Location Information)\n
① The subject of personal location information may defer their consent for part of the scope
of the collection of personal location information and the terms of use, or the usage and purpose
of personal location information, scope of the recipient of personal location information,
and part of location-based services.\n
② Any subject of personal location information may fully or partially withdraw their consent to the collection,
use and provision of personal location information.\n
③ Any subject of personal location information may request, at any time,
a temporary suspension on the collection, use and provision of personal location information.
In such case, the Company shall not refuse such request and shall take technical measures accordingly.\n
④ Any subject of personal location information may request the Company to permit them to inspect any
of the following data or to give notice of any of the following data,
and may request the Company to correct an error found in the concerned data. In such case,
the Company shall not reject such request without good cause:\n
1. Data verifying the collection, use and provision of personal location information
which relates to the subject of personal location information\n
2. The ground on which the personal location information of the subject
of personal location information was provided to a third party pursuant to the provisions
of the Act on the Protection and Use of Location Information or other Acts, and the relevant details.\n
⑤ Where the subject of personal location information fully or partially withdraws their consent,
the Company shall, without delay, destroy the collected personal location information
and the data verifying the collection, use and provision of location information.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, where the subject of personal location information partially withdraws their consent,
such destruction of data is limited to the personal location information and the data verifying the use and provision
of location information for the part withdrawn.\n
⑥ In order to ensure the subject of personal location information exercises their rights under paragraph
(1) or paragraph (4), the subject of personal location information may use the contact information under Article 13
of this agreement to make requests to the Company.\n\n


Article 5 (Rights Held by Legal Representatives)\n
① Where the Company intends to collect, use or provide personal location information
from children under 14 years of age, the Company shall obtain the consent of the child under 14 years
of age and their legal representative.\n
② Where legal representatives provide their consent to the collection,
use and provision of personal location information of children under 14 years of age,
they may exercise the right to defer consent, right to withdraw and suspend consent,
and right to request inspection and notification.\n\n


Article 6 (Grounds for and Period of Retaining Data Verifying the Usage and Provision of Location Information)\n
In accordance with Article 16 (2) of the Act on the Protection and Use of Location Information,
the Company shall automatically record data verifying the collection, use, and provision of location information
in a location information system, and preserve the data for 6 months or longer.\n\n


Article 7 (Changes to and Termination of Services)\n
① Where it becomes impossible for the Company to maintain its services due to various circumstances
of the Company such as policy changes of the location-based service provider or legal obstacles,
the Company may restrict, change or terminate the service fully or partially.\n
② When the service is terminated pursuant to paragraph (1), the Company shall make an announcement
on the Internet or notify the subject of personal location information prior to such termination.\n\n


Article 8 (Immediate Notification when Providing Third Parties with Personal Location Information)\n
① The Company shall not provide the personal location information of the subject of personal location information
to a third party without the consent of the relevant subject of personal location information,
and in the case of providing services offered by a third party, the designated recipient
of the personal location information and the purpose of provision shall be notified to the subject
of personal location information in advance, and shall obtain his/her consent.\n
② In case the Company provides personal location information to a third party designated by the subject
of personal location information, the Company shall immediately notify, on each occasion,
the subject of personal location information, of the designated recipient of such information,
the date, time, and purpose of such provision via the communication terminal device
from which the personal location information was collected.\n\n


Article 9 (Rights Held by the Legal Guardian of Children of Eight Years Old or Younger, etc.)\n
① Where the legal guardian of any of the following persons (hereinafter referred to as
child of eight years old or younger, etc.)
gives consent to the use or provision of personal location information regarding
the child of eight years old or younger, etc., for the protection of the child\&apos;s health or safety,
the Company shall deem that the child, etc. themselves consent thereto:\n
1. A child of eight years old or younger\n
2. A person under adult guardianship\n
3. A person with a mental disorder defined in Article 2 (2) 2 of the Act on Welfare of Persons with Disabilities,
classified as a person with a severe disability defined in subparagraph 2 of Article 2 of the Act
on the Employment Promotion and Vocational Rehabilitation of Persons with Disabilities
(limited to those registered as disabled persons under Article 32 of the Act on Welfare of Persons with Disabilities).\n
② For the protection of the health or safety of a child of eight years old or younger, etc.,
the legal guardian who intends to consent to the use or provision of personal location information must submit
a written consent to the Company along with a document proving that he/she is the legal guardian.\n
③ The legal guardian can exercise all of the rights of the subject of personal location information
if he/she agrees to the use or provision of personal location information
for a child of eight years old or younger,etc.\n\n


Article 10 (Purpose of Retention and Period of Use of Personal Location Information)\n
① The Company shall retain and use personal location information for the minimum period necessary
to provide location-based services.\n
② The Company shall destroy personal location information without delay after one-time
or temporary use from most location-based services.\n\n


Article 11 (Compensation for Damage)\n
Where a subject of personal location information suffers damage because the Company has violated Articles 15 through 26,
he/she may claim damages against the Company. In such cases, the Company shall not be exempt
from liabilities unless it proves that there was no intention or negligence on its part.\n\n


Article 12 (Mediation in Disputes)\n
① Where the parties to a dispute related to location information fail to reach an agreement
or it is impossible to reach an agreement, the Company may file
a petition for adjudication with the Korea Communications Commission.\n
② Where the parties to a dispute related to location information fail to reach an agreement
or it is impossible to reach an agreement, the Company or the subject of personal location information may file
a petition for mediation with the Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee established under
the Personal Information Protection Act.\n\n


Article 13 (Contact and Person Responsible for Location Information)\n
① Name, manager and contact information of the Company are as follows:\n
Department: Don't be late company\n
name : KIM JAE HYUN,LIM CHAE MYUNG,  JANG GYU SIK, CHOI JI WON, PARK HYE LAN\n
rank : Leader, deputy leader, team member, team member, team member\n
contact : onecoin789@gmail.com, limchaem0318@gmail.com, jgs288@gmail.com, sp202401jw@gmail.com, tnfl2644@gmail.com\n\n


    </string>

</resources>